Guide to the Floyd R. Newman papers, 1893-1990.
Newman, Floyd R. papers, 1893-1990
- Travel
  - Hawaii, 1954 -1955, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Houston, Mexico City, Taxco, Acapulco, Fort Worth, Tucson, Grand Canyon, Los Angeles, Honolulu, Island of Maui, and Seattle, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Weather - A.R.W. (from Holiday) (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - "Epicurean Tour of the French Provinces," 1949 -1951 (Gourmet) (Box 21, Folder 17-20)
  - NYC - inactive (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Travel - letters - memos - itineraries, 1964 -1974 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Norwich, Vermont, Boston, Mass., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Mexico (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Canada (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Cuba - West Indies - South America (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Spain - Portugal (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Vendors - European and others (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Paris (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - France, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Switzerland, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Switzerland - Liechtenstein (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Italy (Box 21, Folder 33-34)
  - Luxembourg - Holland - Belgium (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Germany, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Planning folder - Germany, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 2-4)
  - Austria (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Sweden and Scandinavian countries (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Austria, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - England - Great Britain (Box 22, Folder 8-10)
  - Europe - general (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Hawaii - general, 1957 -1974 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Motels, hotels, motor travel, maps, etc., 1965 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Hotels, itineraries, various - RTW (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - RTW, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Hong Kong (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Visa - Mainland China, 1973 -1974 - efforts to obtain visa (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - China (Box 22, Folder 18-20)
  - Zurich, Bodensee, Tegernsee, Bad Kissingen, Frankfort, Hamburg, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - London - England (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Paris, Morocco, Madrid, London, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - Germany - Wurzburg, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 3-6)
  - Germany, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Germany - R.S. Blazer (Frank Sargent) (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Luxembourg, 1918 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Copenhagen - Stockholm - Mariehamn, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Switzerland (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Rome (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Japan, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 13-14)
  - Middle East, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 15-16)
  - Asian countries (UAR), 1962 (Box 23, Folder 17-18)
  - Holland, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
  - Japan, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 3-4)
  - Germany (Box 24, Folder 5-11)
  - Italy, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Normandy - North and Northeast of France, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 13-14)
  - Paris - various, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 15-16)
  - Italy, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
  - France - general - maps, etc., 1952 (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
  - Paris to the Riviera, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 5-6)
  - The Riviera, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - England, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 8-10)
  - Europe - general (Box 25, Folder 11-12)
  - Sweden, Stockholm, 1952; Finland, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 13-16)
  - London (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Great Britain (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Denmark, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
  - Austria, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 5- 6)
  - Luxembourg, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Belgium, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 8-9)
  - Germany, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 10-12)
  - Italy - maps (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Switzerland, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 14-16)
  - Italy, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Paris, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Luxembourg, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Switzerland, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Switzerland, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Tours and vicinity, 1949; St. Tropez; Nice and vicinity (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Italy, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Nice and Monte Carlo (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Luxembourg, Germany (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - France, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - London, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - France, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Various (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Sweden, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Holland, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - "Queen Mary" (menus), 1948 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - "Queen Mary" (various), 1948 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - "Queen Elizabeth," 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - "Queen Mary" (menus), 1949 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - "Nieuw Amsterdam" (menus), 1949 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - "Queen Mary," 1949 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Middle East, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - United Arab Republic, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 19-20)
  - Japan - greeting cards, ca. 1959 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Holland, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 22-23)
  - Italy, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Germany, Frankfort - phrase books, German wines, various (Box 28, Folder 1-3)
  - Florence (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Siena, Venice, Pisa (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook material - 1956, 1958, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Japan - scrapbook material, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Japan - hotel labels and scrapbook material, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - 'Round the World scrapbook material, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 9-10)
  - Book #1 (travel notes) - 1948 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Book #2 (travel notes) - 1949 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Books #1 2 (travel notes) - 1952 (Box 28, Folder 13-14)
  - Hawaiian Islands and Japan (also S.F. and Seattle) -(travel notes) - 1955 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Books #1 2 (travel notes) - Europe, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 16-17)
  - Brussels, Paris, Luxembourg, Dusseldorf and vicinity (travel notes) - 1958 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Books #1 2 (travel notes) - Orient, etc., 1959 (Box 28, Folder 19-20)
  - Hemlock Hollow - Oklahoma, Texas and the far west (travel notes) - 1960 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - To Frankfort Germany, Zurich, Bodensee, Munich, Bavaria (travel notes) - 1960 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Holland (Amsterdam), Brussels (travel notes) - 1962 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Books #1 2 - data, etc. up to and including India, Casablanca and Marrakech (travel notes) - 1962 -63 (Box 28, Folder 24-25)
  - To Copenhagen, Mariehamn, Stockholm (and Strangnas), Germany and Luxembourg (travel notes) - 1964 (from International and Return) (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - To Paris, Morocco (Casablanca, Rabat and Marrakech), Madrid and London (travel notes) - 1965 (from International and Return) (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Books #1 2 - Hamburg, Baden-Baden and Wiesbaden, etc. (travel notes) - 1967; Christening of Caroline Neumann, Hamburg, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 28-29)
  - To Zurich, Konstanz, etc. (travel notes) - 1971 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Churchville - Shanghai, 1912 -1916 (Box 28, Folder 31-34)
  - Miscellaneous guide books including Italy, Japan, France (Box 28, Folder 35-41)
- Cornell Miscellany
  - Admissions Office (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Athletics - football: R.L. Blackman, 1980 -1982; Maxie Baughan, 1984 -1988; Jim Hofher, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Athletics - basketball: Tom Miller, 1983 -1986; Michael Dement, 1986 -1990 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Athletics - Laing E. Kennedy, 1983 -1990 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Athletics - Terry Mallett, 1983 -1985 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Athletics - Michael L. Slive, 1981 -1983 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Barton Hall - LTC David J. Boyle, 1983 -1984 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Barton Hall - Gerald J. Hone LTC (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Michael P. Browne, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Swan Connell (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Communique articles and Cornell Alumni News, 1987 -1988 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Forensics Society, 1988 -1990 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Forensics Society, 1986 -1987 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Forensics Society, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Forensics Society, 1983 -1984 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Forensics Society, 1980 -1981 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Hotel School (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Cornell University North Central Regional Office (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Plantations, 1985 -1989 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Plantations, 1981 -1984 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Plantations - newspaper articles (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Cornell Personnel
  - Martha Arnett, 1980 -1986 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Robert A. Beck, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Hans Bethe (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Clayton Chapman, 1969 -1970 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Gould P. Colman, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Dale R. Corson, 1970 -1990 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Edmund E. Day, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - David R. Dunlop, 1987 -1990 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - David R. Dunlop, 1976 -1986 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Sol Goldberg, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - William G. Herbster, 1983 -1987 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Robert T. Horn, 1967 -1988 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Raymond F. Howes, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - William W. Ruling, Jr., 1986 -1989 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Robert J. Kane, 1971 -1989 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - W. Keith Kennedy (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - George S. Kephart (Plantations) (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Austin H. Kiplinger (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Richard M. Lewis (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Allyn B. Ley, M.D. (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - C. Richard Lynham, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Deane W. Malott (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Boyce D. McDaniel, 1980 -1985 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Thomas H. Meikle, Jr. M.D., 1982 -1987 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - National Rowing Foundation, 1965 -1967 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Jack E. Oliver, 1984 -1989 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - Jack E. Oliver, 1974 -1983 (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - Charles E. Palm, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - James A. Perkins, 1966 -1969 (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - Robert W. Purcell, 1980 -1990 (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - Richard M. Ramin, 1979 -1990 (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - Frank H. "T. Rhodes, 1986 -1990 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Frank H. T. Rhodes, 1977 -1985 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Andrew Schultz, Jr., 1980 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Neal R. Stamp (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - W. Barlow Ware (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Kenneth G. Wilson, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Robert R. Wilson, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Floyd R. Newman Friends
  - Ahmad Gaafar, son - Mahmoud, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Robert C. Gill, 1981 -1982 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Dr. R. T. Goodwin, 1969 -1973 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Mack and Libby Gordon (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Joseph G. Grossman, 1963 -1983 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Dr. Farid Sami Haddad, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Eleanor Beaumont Hartman (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Kay Heasley (Mrs. Walter C.), 1879 -1984 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - William A. Holcombe, 1983 -1986 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - George and Julie (Kuchler) Holmes (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Austin 0. Hooey, 1979 -1987 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - S.K. Kawana, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Graham "Pat" Kearney, Lisbon, Ohio, 1912 M.E., d. Apr. 1, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Vijay Khanna, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Mahadev Prasad Khann, 1963 -1968; Jagdish Khanna, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Marcel and Renee Kieffer - also Fernand Kieffer (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - George W. Kuchler, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Nagahide Kuroda, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Nagahide (and Linda) Kuroda (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - 1. Correspondence and file, Paper Coatings and Clay, USA, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - 2. Trip to USA (Naga and Linda), 1964 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Jon A. Lindseth, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Lucien S. Loeb, 1978 -1982 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Wallace M. Luthy (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Walter E. Lutz (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - James I. and Daria Maresh - Around the World (International Study Group Project), 1972 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Toshitatsu and Masuko Mayeda (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Loren J. and Alma Mead; also Cynthia and Don Mead, 1979 -1985 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Medina Community Services Center, Charity (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Charles B. Merrill (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Jack L. Minner (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence A thru M (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence O thru Z (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Charles H. and Bethine Alberding, 1982 -1988 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Elaine Mead Alexander (Mrs. John J.)/ 1977 -1980 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Robert W. Baggs, Jr. (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Peter H. Bame (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Robert M. Bartlett (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - Berea College (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - Gerald M. Best (Harriet), 1980 -1984 (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - Gerald M. Best (Harriet), 1968 -1979 (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - Walter S. and Jane Betts (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - William P. Boyle, Jr. (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - Frances 0. Briggs; also Lynton I. Briggs, 1978 -1990 (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - John W. and Ruth Brothers (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - Cecil A. Brown (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - Michael J. Browne (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - Walter G. Bruska, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 53)
  - Clifford R. Carter, 1978 -1982 (Box 31, Folder 54)
  - Mark F. Chenevey, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 55)
  - Richard C.B. Clark, 1981 -1987 (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - Wood M. DeYoe; also Leon DeYoe, 1975 -1983 (Box 31, Folder 57)
  - O.D. Oilier, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 58)
  - Donald Duke of Golden West Books, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 59)
  - Dorset Hotel, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 60)
  - David C. and Mildred Duncan, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 61)
  - Gustave Egloff, 1947 -1949 (Box 31, Folder 62)
  - Resi Esper, et al (Box 31, Folder 63)
  - Walter Fiessler, 1978 -1985 (Box 31, Folder 64)
  - Roger Flandre, 1981 -1985 (Box 31, Folder 65)
  - Lee R. Forker, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 66)
  - Mrs. Dewey E. (Dorothy) Foster, 1977 -1982 (Box 31, Folder 67)
  - Grace Kuchler Foster, 1977 -1990 (Box 31, Folder 68)
  - Lee W. Foster, 1979 -1988 (Box 31, Folder 69)
  - H. Y. Mo and family (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - J. Y. Mo (loan), 1959 -1971 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Florence (Mrs. Clarence W.) Moore, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - James Navratil (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Alien B. Norton (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Edwin T. Ohishi (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Itaru Ohki, 1971 -1973 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Seinosake and Takako Ozaki (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Ernest and Betty (Kuchler) Palmquist (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Mary Pan (Hong Kong), 1969 -1976 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - F. Stuart Pease, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Robert N. Peck, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - S. Alden Perrine, 1971 -1985 (Box 32, Folder 13-14)
  - Perry A. Peterson (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Prasad - Khanna, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Mahadev Prasad; New Delhi; London; Ithaca; Philadelphia; Lachman Dass; Wharton School; Philadelphia; Maresh Khanna; Cornell, Graduate School of Business; Deane W. Malott, President; Vijay K. Khanna; Edward I. flash, Jr., Director of Admissions (Box 32, Folder 17-18)
  - Frank A. Ready, Jr. (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Rae and Richard Reynolds (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Karl Ritter (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - John Schivell - Western Reserve Academy, 1955 -1959 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Charles W. Scott, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Hiroshi Shimamura (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Maranjan Singh (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Donald L. and Mildred Smith (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - John J. Steitz, Jr., 1971 -1974 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Fred W. Stewart (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Harry Temple, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Richard T. Vail (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Vaningen Family (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Norman Waldheger (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - John Watson, 1977 -1982 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - R.E. Webster, 1952 -1953 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - James A. Weeks (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Willet F. Whitmore, Jr. (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Herbert C. Winter, 1982 -1984 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Miles and Gladys Wiseman, 1977 -1981 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Yuji A. Yamaguchi (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Robert A. Young/Jay S. Carnathon, 1975 -1987 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - John d. Ziegler (son of John H.) (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - John H. and Rosario Ziegler (Box 32, Folder 42)
- Cornell University Miscellany
  - Helen Newman Hall - dedication (room assignment list), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Helen Newman Hall - programs, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - Builders of Cornell (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - Kenroku Garden, Toshitatsu Mayeda, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - Japanese Screen correspondence, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - Professorships - John A. Newman, James A. Weeks, 1973 Cornell Chronicle, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - Professorship of Nuclear Studies given by HAN, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - 1. Internal Revenue Service ruling, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - 2. Internal Revenue Service ruling 60-370, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 50)
- Correspondence, 1908 -1919
  - 1908 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Jan.-May 1909 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Oct.-Nov. 1909 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Jan.-June 1909 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Sept.-Dec. 1910 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Jan.-June 1911 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Sept.-Dec. 1911 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Jan.-Apr. 1912 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - May-July 1912 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Aug. 1912 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Sept.-Nov. 1912 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Dec. 1912 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Jan.-Mar. 1913 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Apr.-May 1913 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - June-Aug. 1913 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Sept.-Dec. 1913 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Jan.-Apr. 1914 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - May-July 1914 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Aug.-Oct. 1914 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Nov.-Dec. 1914 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Jan.-Mar. 1915 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Apr.-June 1915 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - July-Sept. 1915 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Oct.-Dec. 1915 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - Jan.-Apr. 1916 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - May-July 1916 (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - 1917 -1919 (Box 76, Folder 27)
- Miscellany
  - Shanghai Journal, 1912 -1915 (Box 76, Folder 28-34)
  - Churchville High School Drawing, Books 1 and 2, 1903 (Box 76, Folder 35-36)
  - Volume: Natural Advanced Geography dated by FRN September 3, 1901 (Box 76, Folder 37)
  - Confirmation certificate, 1881, of FRN's mother